{
    "subject": "Nancy_Carell",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Steve_Carell",
    "human_readable": "Nancy Carell is married to Steve Carell.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9487370848655701,
            "question": "To whom is Nancy Carell married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9412391781806946,
            "question": "Who is Nancy Carell married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.924387514591217,
            "question": "Is Steve Carell married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.917304277420044,
            "question": "Are Nancy and Steve Carell a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9085684418678284,
            "question": "What is Steve Carell's relationship to Nancy Carell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875636458396912,
            "question": "Are Nancy and Steve Carell together?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773681104183197,
            "question": "Is Nancy Carell in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7608460783958435,
            "question": "Who is Nancy Carell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.756859540939331,
            "question": "What kind of relationship do Nancy and Steve Carell share?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7193920612335205,
            "question": "Who is Steve Carell?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nancy Carell is married to Steve Carell.",
            "html": "yago_30364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of relationship do Nancy and Steve Carell share?",
            "html": "yago_30364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Nancy Carell?",
            "html": "yago_30364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Nancy Carell in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30364_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple confirmations that Nancy Carell has been married to Steve Carell since 1995, and they have two children together. Therefore, the triple \"Nancy Carell is married to Steve Carell\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided in multiple documents, which consistently state that Steve Carell and Nancy Carell are married."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}